I came to Chinatown today to visit.
There's one more person here.
He's running late.
Late? You mean...
That girl.
He's waiting for you.
He'll be here shortly.
Oh...
Pee
LOL!
LOL
Why do you do that?
Hi, it's me, Heala. We're going to Chinatown today.
Are you excited?
I'm so excited!
I'm glad.
Beautiful weather.
Ahhh...
I'm scared.
What do you want to eat? I haven't eaten since this morning.
I want strawberry ramen.
And of course, steamed buns.
I like buns with a lot of skin.
They're good.
Where's Chinatown?
Have you been to Chinatown?
I was in Equal Love with Choco and Hana.
We were in Chinatown with Choco and Hana.
That's right!
So many people!
That means it's Chinatown.
Maybe.
You coming?
It's going down.
Down here?
He says he's a checkman. He's a checkman. He's a checkman.
So we're just gonna settle on this one?
I'm starving.
Can I have a couple of stinkbugs?
What?
Somewhere else.
Let's compare walls.
Can a bear have two pieces?
Can a bear eat two or more?
Can a bear eat two of these?
Oh, my God. I can't see anything.
It's huge.
It's huge. I've never had one this big before. Eat it.
Can I have some?
It looks so good. Bon appétit.
You said you wanted a lot of these, right?
That's great!
We haven't even gotten to the meat yet.
I love it.
One more bite and you'll get there.
Bon appétit.
Yum!
Yummy?
Delicious!
I've never tasted a steamed bun like this.
They're so good, aren't they?
I could eat as many as I want.
Wait, there it is!
How's it going?
Did you get there?
Yes, I'm getting there. I'm getting there, but I'm not there.
But I love this bun.
It looks good with buns.
I don't know...
Do I look good with steamed buns? I've never seen it before.
Your face is too small for a bun.
What? A meat bun.
It's more than a manjuu.
His face is smaller than a steamed bun.
Ha-ha-ha.
Are you full already?
It was bigger than I thought it would be.
I finished mine.
No more meat?
Let's go drink tapioca.
Can I?
Yes.
You're almost done.
But I'm a little hungry.
But you know what? I want to eat some chuganmen.
And I want a drink at Ryokan.And I want to drink Ryokan.
I want to eat a Shuman.
And I want another Big Man.
One more?
I'm going out.
I don't think I can.
Thank you for the food.
All done.
Let's go get a drink.
Okay.
I want something fun.
That fat one.
Chicken?
It's famous.
Maybe I'll just do that and go home.
I'll take it home.
Where is tapioca?
Tapioca. I can only drink strawberry milk.
I like good.
Here you go.
Oh, they have strawberry milk!
We have strawberry milk.
Do you have brown sugar?
Yes, I do.
Look.
I'm crushing your food before you know it.
You're scaring me.
I think it's my palm.
Have you seen my palm?
It's number three.
That's the worst.
He asked me if I wanted a palm reading.
We're going after this, right?
That's right.
See you.
Strawberry milk
Brown sugar milk.
I've never seen a slaw like this before.
Not with tapioca.
I don't have much either.
Bon appétit!
Bon appétit.
Mmm.
It's sticky.
Delicious.
You look the same.
We don't have the same face.
Do we look alike?
I think we look more alike.
Of the collaborators.
Of the collaborators?
Really?
If we had the same hair, we'd probably look alike.
Whispering and stuff.
Whisper, whisper, whisper.
Whisper, whisper, whisper, whisper...
whisper, whisper, whisper.
Sarcasm.
Are you okay? I'd love to, but...
But I'm so hungry.
I'm so full.
I'd love to.
I'd like to eat a basket of dumplings, too.
This guy's amazing.
It's amazing!
It's like Spirited Away.
It's like a thousand and one things.
Strawberry candies... They're all over the place.
What's so good about it?
What's good about it?
I'm drinking everything with strawberries.
How much longer are we going to do this?
As far as it goes.
I don't know.
You keep coming at me like that.
I'm leaning towards you because I have a distance bug.
Bugged? Watch me.
I lean on people.
We always bump shoulders.
Always bumping into each other.
And I always step on their feet or get stepped on.
It's all my fault.
That's right.
Next time we find strawberry lozenges, we'll buy strawberry lozenges.
Okay.
I found it.
Can I have a strawberry lozenge?
No.
It's right here.It's right here.
I wonder who's the real deal.
Can I eat for the first time in a while?
Sure.
First time?
Yeah, first time.
Alive?
Yeah, it's my first time.
I've never bought anything before.
I... I...
Bon appétit.
What are you gonna do with it?
You want some?
Mmm.
That much?
Wow.
It's good.
Is it good?
Good for you.
We can eat it like yakitori.
Yeah, that's right.
That's what I'm talking about.
Here's another one.
This one stuck to my mouth like crazy.
Mmmm...
Mmm-hmm.
Oh!
Pick it up.
Ready?
Nnn, it doesn't work.
Ichigo-chan...
You really live in a mysterious world, Kiara-chan.
Why do I have to eat strawberry candy, too?
Go!
Wait, I might break it.
I might end up like me again.
How do you eat it?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, it's good.
Oh, it's good! That's it.
It's cold! It's cold, right?
Frozen!
Delicious!
So crunchy? Crunchy?
ASMR!
It's cold! Are you okay?
It's cold!
Cold?
Because I saw the way you eat, Mayuka.
Turn it! Turn it!
Turn it!
Just turn it!
Just eat it like a kebab.
I've never had a kebab.
Like a saltilla.
What are you talking about?
I'm at the cafe.
I'm here.
We've eaten a lot.
So we're going to sit down and take a break.
It was hot.
We have parasols.
That's fine.
Don't stop the sense in your hands.
Oh, here he comes.
Oh, he's not stopping, is he?
He's running like crazy.
I thought I'd like to keep going.
That was fun.